Hello hello viewers welcome to Tiwari
Strongroom channel friends in today's video
we will examine the fundamentals of SSC Lamba General Insurance Company
and try to understand
why we should invest
in this stock or the general insurance
sector for long-term profit friends there was
an article in Naukri Times on the
basis of which they are telling that General
Insurance can be sold at 729,
these can be sold at 52210 let us know that the
leading companies of the sector like today the longest
General Insurance company will start from mode nine percent
friends in this video we will try to
know about the general insurance industry
then we will see whether the
growth and position in the sector is good and how big it
is so friends as we know that the
growth in wealth of any stock can be full
when there are a lot of opportunities in it
then after that we will know about the company, we will
go about its different business aspects then we will see the revenue backup of the company, how much
money the company earns from the segment, we will
see the different factors of that company, finally you
will see its validation and finally  I am my
tag, friends, in 21 ways
we get lighters in this company, we should invest in them, so
friends, if you liked the video, then
like and subscribe to the channel so
that
you do not get time for future informative videos and
you can make your investment in the right way, so
friends, let us start the video, so
friends, now let us understand India's general insurance
industry,
where it stands at the level and on the global footprint,
friends, and how much is the giver subsidy here, then by dividing it
into toke, we come to know
that India's non-life insurance
market is in a perfect position,
if we look at the global market, at the global level,
India's general insurance
industry, on the flavor, if we
talk about non-life insurance printer,
is less than great, friends, we
can bring the channel even more, then there is a loss,
PM has cent of GDP per US dollar, on this
basis also we look at all the global
countries, like Indonesia has 0.5
percent, India has 1%, Russia has 1% and
we talk about advanced countries
like Japan, its  UK is 2.4,
South Africa is 2.3, South Korea is 2.5, and South Korea is 5.2. If we
look at it, then it is nine per cent of
GDP. On the advice of friends, we see
that the growth opportunity is very real,
friends. And there is a loss
on the premium. If we
look at it Yudhishthir, then this no. 100 per capita of India, let us
talk about Indonesia's 24900, Japan's is
96960 and we can leave it that it is
very real, 98100 per capita.
So on this basis, we are seeing
that the group posts received in this sector are
very real, friends. So, the
companies of this chapter, like ICC General Insurance
Company, which we are talking about in this video,
friends, they have
multi-fold opposition to growth. So, friends, if we
talk about some factors which will be
helpful against the general insurance industry of India, then the first important
factor that we find after searching for is the great Indian
middle class, that people in India who have come from the soil.
Now we are living in this way,
friends, so subscribed on this side, the
public will buy motor cars, there are
villages that
can come in,
Shravan is a quarter inch factor, young insurance
population, so friends, you are seeing that and
see, there is a country and here there are
more than 5231 groups, it is increasing in a very long time,
friends, on this we are seeing that there is a lot of
opposition from the population,
hatred population for
true life insurance scheme, friends, it is becoming a
cancer in the appointment, that we are
obscene, so on this basis the
market of the accused will increase, friends and fourth, the
important
development
IRDA has made it clear that
you can take it through some other video, do
subscribe, it will be
very beneficial in giving air to the channel,
friends, friends, now let us
know about this Lamba General Insurance Company
or Fielding and Step by
Step General Insurance Company of India, which was
established
in 2019 as a joint venture between Bank and Fairfax Financial Holdings, where you have that
its joint venture partner
limited,
so friends, it has come out and what was its own  It was done
in 2008, so friends, now let's
talk about the business version of the company. The
total business of the company is
divided into its products. First is Aircraft Solutions,
second is Government and World Business
Group, third is Detail Group and Chinese
Share Service. Friends, the
Corporate Group of this company provides Play Services,
benefits to corporate and meat
market companies across and active,
a specialized industry group that
works in the last line specialized businessmen,
Prince Roshni supports them.
Similarly, it
also provides insurance pension products for small and medium enterprises group
and also provides depression to provide international risk cover to such Indian
companies which operate worldwide.
Friends, here the
company has Insurance Solutions for
Naren for Engineering Division for
Liability Services, Employer
Group Insurance, Cyber ​​Insurance, Health
Personal Insurance, Accident Cover, which is
provided to these groups. Friends, the
second business division of the company is its
Government Under Ruler Business Form, which
provides insurance solutions.  This is the
Institute of Central Government, State
Government and Enterprises and Ruler
Customers, where this organization is providing
personal accident and motor insurance for cattle verification, meat health and other solutions,
which is provided by Inspector Singh Roots.
So, its third division
is its retail group, where the
company has provided insurance services to individuals and Ismail Enterprises
through exams, brokerage,
bank insurance, tele sales, director
license, motor insurance,
through forgiveness or through online
platform, which is provided to the retail group.
In this chapter, the company is subscribing to health, home,
motorable, cyber security, personal
accident cover, this solution is
for India, friends, so
friends, the fourth division of this company is
its service services division, and this
division is a rights organization that
works towards increasing customer service and gypsy. Here the company has
handwriting and claims, customer
relations, technology operations, free
insurance, finance, account, human
resources.  The company is providing different services like Legal and Compliance, Rural
Marketing, Business Analytics,
Administration and Flood Control
for its inter-organizational services.
So friends, now let us
look at the portfolio backup of this company to see
how much revenue is generated from which sector.
Friends, in this company, the
gross return
premium of the company was 2030 per quarter, where Motor on
Damage is 22%, you have GWP.
After this, third party of motor generates 22%
revenue. Similarly, Help,
Travel and Personal Accident is at 22%, which
is 70%, Marine 777
Protection is five percent and there
services generate nine percent revenue of this company.
Friends, now we talk about the valuations of the company,
as we are seeing that the
sprint share price of this company is
thirteen to zero and the investigation team of this company is
30 2011 and 2030
06 friends, so on this basis we  We see that
this company is just about to cross its 22nd,
so friends, this is the
best point where we
should initiate investment in this company for
long-term verification, friends. And any
position trade that can be done below, can also
start investment at this point.
Friends, let us look at the valuation of the company on its
back basis. At present, the
back of the company is around
50.9 and the medium value of this company is
15.1, friends. So, we are seeing
that the company is at a pimpled valuation. If we look at the
Gari Team GPS of this company, it is around 15.1, so on
this
basis, we are looking at the company's business in
Balochistan. Here, we should initiate investment in our company
for long-term verification,
friends. Now, we
look at the business conditions of this company on the basis of different rates, 521. The commission of this company is
69 percent and the commission of this company
is 6 percent combined.  Aggressive
hundred percent friends, solvency
is 20% in that, net retention is sure 75%, so
friends, if you want to know about these relationships, then
please tell us by commenting, then
we will make an accepted video of it and
tell you, the meaning of the initial in it is so
friends, now let us
look at the different meters of the company, the
market cap of the company is
52.4, the company's charge is
26.94, the accused is 21.7, debt to equity company
is 27.4, so on this basis
also we see that the business of this company is very
lucrative and there is full possibility
of long-term wealth creation in this company,
friends, any
investor who wants to do long-term wealth creation
correction from the stock market should
definitely invest in this segment and in this company, so
friends,
please tell us by commenting how you liked the video, and if
you are new to the channel, then
definitely subscribe to the channel so that
you can get time for upcoming important videos.  If you could not find it
and were able to take your investment decision correctly, then
friends, thank you for watching the video.